<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MovieTicketOrder</string>
    <string name="title_app">BiosTix</string>
    <string name="aggreement1">By Creating an account, you agree to Application</string>
    <string name="aggreement2">Term of Use and Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="bawah3">Doesnt have an account yet?</string>
    <string name="bawah4">Register</string>
    <string name="btn_login">LogIn</string>
    <string name="greet">Hello,</string>
    <string name="placeholder_1">User</string>
    <string name="Question">What movie do you want to watch?</string>
    <string name="title_description">Available Movies</string>
    <string name="btn_order">Order Now</string>
    <string name="payment_title">Payment</string>

    <array name="title">
        <item>All Quite on the Western Front</item>
        <item>Suzume no Tojimari</item>
        <item>Barbie</item>
        <item>Ballerina</item>
        <item>Interstellar</item>
        <item>Oppenheimer</item>
        <item>Bullet Train</item>
        <item>Tennet</item>
    </array>

    <array name="description">
        <item>it follows the life of an idealistic young German soldier named Paul Bäumer.
            After enlisting in the German Army with his friends, Bäumer finds himself exposed to the
            realities of war,
            shattering his early hopes of becoming a hero as he does his best to survive.
        </item>
        <item>17-year-old Suzume who meets a mysterious young man named Souta looking for a door in
            the mountains.
            Suzume later finds out that the door is one of many appearing in lonely areas across
            Japan
            that are responsible for various disasters.
        </item>
        <item>Set in the colorful Barbie Land, stereotypical Barbie lives a perfect life every
            single day.
            One day, she shows signs of being...a human. She decides to go to the Real World to find
            the cure
            in order to make herself perfect again.
        </item>
        <item>Ok-Ju is good at physical activities such as martial arts, sword fighting,
            marksmanship, and motorbike riding.
            Ok-Ju is friends with Min-Hee, who is a ballerina. One day, Ok-Ju found Min-Hee dead at
            her house.
        </item>
        <item>Earth last chance to find a habitable planet before a lack of resources causes the
            human race to go extinct.
            The film protagonist is Cooper (Matthew McConaughey), a former NASA pilot who is tasked
            with leading a mission
            through a wormhole to find a habitable planet in another galaxy.
        </item>
        <item>In 1942, during World War II, U.S. Army General Leslie Groves recruits Oppenheimer
            to lead the Manhattan Project to develop an atomic bomb. Oppenheimer, who is Jewish,
            is particularly driven by the Nazis potentially completing their nuclear weapons
            program, headed by Heisenberg.
        </item>
        <item>ichi Kimura, (The Father), boards a bullet train in Tokyo in search of the attacker of
            his son Wataru.
            Meanwhile, guided by his handler Maria Beetle, assassin (Ladybug) is assigned to
            retrieve a briefcase full of cash
            from the same train, replacing a sick colleague, Carver.
        </item>
        <item>The film follows a former CIA agent who is recruited into a secretive organization
            called "Tenet"
            who can reverse the flow of time and is trying to prevent an attack from the future that
            threatens
            to annihilate the present world.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="Director">
        <item>Edward Berger</item>
        <item>Makoto Shinkai</item>
        <item>Greta Gerwig</item>
        <item>Lee Chung-hyeon</item>
        <item>Christopher Nolan</item>
        <item>Christopher Nolan</item>
        <item>David Leitch</item>
        <item>Christopher Nolan</item>
    </array>

    <array name="Bioskop">
        <item>XXI Jogja City Mall</item>
        <item>Empire XXI </item>
        <item>XXI Plaza Ambarukmo</item>
        <item>CGV Pakuwon Mall</item>
        <item>Cinepolis Lippo Plaza</item>
        <item>Sleman City Hall XXI</item>
        <item>CGV Jwalk Mall</item>
    </array>

    <array name="Jenis_Seat">
        <item>Reguler</item>
        <item>Premiere</item>
        <item>VIP</item>
    </array>

    <array name="Bank">
        <item>BCA</item>
        <item>BNI</item>
        <item>BRI</item>
        <item>BSI</item>
        <item>MANDIRI</item>
    </array>

</resources>